[{"id": 2844, "question": "I want to let you know about an event that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Sunday morning. We decided to stop at a local gas station to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as if he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something to drink. However, it was not this that moved me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog lover, I noticed that the dog was a mother and that she had just had some puppies . She was hungry and weak and I felt so bad for her. I knew if she di...\n\nQ: The author did the following except that he  _  .", "options": ["had pity on the dog that was in danger", "bought dog food with all the money he had", "was a person who treasured dogs very much", "went home from Houston one Sunday morning"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 299, "question": "Some years ago on a hot summer day in south Florida a little boy decided to go for a swim in the old swimming hole behind his house.In a hurry to dive into the cool water, he ran out of the back door, leaving behind shoes, socks, and shirt as he went. He flew into the water, not realizing that as he swam toward the middle of the lake, a crocodile was swimming toward him.His mother in the house was looking out of the window and saw the two.In great fear, she ran toward the water, shouting to her son as loudly as she could.Hearing her voice, the little boy became alarmed and made a U-turn to swim to his mother.It was too late.Just as he reached her, the crocodile reached him.From the shore, the mother grabbed her little boy by the arms just as the crocodile snatched his legs.That began an in...\n\nQ: Hearing Mother's shouts, the boy  _  .", "options": ["remained in the middle at a loss", "didn't stop swimming forwards", "swam back towards the shore", "was ready to fight the crocodile"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 66, "question": "New research at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis shows that people who struggle with mood problems or addiction can safely quit smoking and that kicking the habit is associated with improved mental health. Cavazos-Rehg, an assistant professor of psychiatry, found that quitting or significantly cutting back on cigarette smoking was linked to improved mental health outcomes. Quitting altogether or reducing by half the number of cigarettes smoked daily was associated with lower risk for mood disorders like depression, as well as a lower likelihood of alcohol and drug problems. \"We don't know if their mental health improves first and then they are more motivated to quit smoking or if quitting smoking leads to an improvement in mental health,\" Cavazos-Rehg said. \"But either...\n\nQ: Which of the following does professor Cavazos-Rehg agree?", "options": ["Quitting smoking leads to a better psychiatric outlook.", "If you want to quit smoking, you have to improve your mood problems first.", "There is a strong link between mental health and quitting smoking.", "There is no need to stop smoking when patients center on mental health."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3015, "question": "We might not be alone in the universe. Actually, it may be confirmed as a very crowded place by new computer models developed to help identify habitable planets. Estimates of places where life can exist have been based on the possibility of them having surface water. But software recently developed by the Aberdeen University allows researchers to identify planets with underground water kept liquid by heat from planets. Water is fundamental for life and planets too close to the sun lose water to the atmosphere through evaporation. On the other hand, planets located in distant reaches from their star have their surface water locked away as ice. Sean McMahon, who is carrying out the work, explained: \"Traditionally people have said that if a planet is in this Goldilocks zone--not too hot and n...\n\nQ: What theory is the Aberdeen team's study based on?", "options": ["Planets can lose water through evaporation.", "Planets can receive heat direct from the star.", "Planets can have their surface water locked away as ice.", "Planets can receive heat generated deep inside the planet."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1478, "question": "A person named Bernard Jackson today is a free man, but he has many bitter memories. He spent five years in prison after a jury wrongly convicted (...) him of raping two women. At Jackson's trial, although two witnesses testified that Jackson was with them in another location at the time of the crime, he was convicted anyway. Why? The jury believed the testimony of the two victims, who positively identified Jackson as the man who had attacked them. The court eventually freed Jackson after the police found the real criminal. Many factors influence the accuracy of eyewitness testimony. For instance, witnesses sometimes see photographs of several suspects before they try to identify the person they saw in a group of people. They can become confused by seeing many photographs of similar faces....\n\nQ: The following statements may be the reasons for why sometimes the eyewitness' testimony is not accurate EXCEPT    _   .", "options": ["the eyewitness is confused by the police's questions", "the eyewitness is shown photos of many similar faces", "the eyewitness lacks the professional help from police", "the eyewitness can't identify people of other races clearly."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1638, "question": "One day a student went to see his teacher. He had been given an important position and now was coming to say goodbye to his teacher. The old man asked him how he would live among high officials. The student answered, \" I will be all right. I have prepared a hundred high hats, one for each official I will meet. I am sure I will succeed.\" The teacher got angry on hearing this. \"What?\" he cried. \"Is this what ten years of my teaching has made of you? Nothing but flatterer ?\" \"Excuse me, honored master,\" the student rose to his feet and apologized hurriedly. \"But you have always been absorbed in your studies and don't know how vulgar the world has come to be. There are few men in the world who are above flatterers like you.\" \"There is something true in what you said,\" the teacher nodded, smili...\n\nQ: The teacher  _  .", "options": ["liked to be flattered as well", "really knew nothing about the vulgar world", "was in need of a high hat", "was satisfied with the new hat"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2281, "question": "Where can you find a nice place to relax on holiday for both you and your children? Well, I suggest you try the beautiful and green Isle of Wight (IOW). The Isle of Wight is one of the main tourist attractions. Here is some information on a few of the attractions on the IOW. Dinosaur Isle It is located in Sandown, a seaside town on the southeast coast. It's a large, lovely museum, both fun and educational. Here you can see a large fossil collection of all kinds of dinosaurs, as well as a gift shop. You can walk into the past and then the future, learning about the history and the development of the civilization of dinosaurs that lived 120 million years ago. Robin Hill Country Park The park is in the beautiful countryside, and is suitable for children's parties and games. It has five new ga...\n\nQ: Where can you learn something as well as have a good time?", "options": ["Dinosaur Isle and Robin Hill Country Park.", "Dinosaur Isle and the West of the Wight.", "The Wight Bus Museum and Robin Hill Country Park.", "The Wight Bus Museum and the West of the Wight."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3119, "question": "Chocolate soap is supposed to be good for the skin. But it's not so good for the tongue. Unfortunately for the US soldiers of World War II, the chocolate bars the army gave them tasted like they were intended for use in the bath. In the army's defense, it wasn't trying to win any cooking awards. In fact, it specifically ordered that its chocolate bars not be too delicious, so soldiers wouldn't eat them too quickly. These bars were created for survival, not taste. \"They were awful,\" John Otto, a former army captain in World War II said, \"They were big, thick things, and they weren't any good. I tried them, but I had to be awfully hungry after I tried them once.\" As unappealing as the chocolate bars were to some, others like them. Samuel Hinkle, the chemist who created the chocolate bars, po...\n\nQ: Elizabeth Radsma never saw chocolate during the war because   _  .", "options": ["the US soldiers never showed up in the small town she lived in", "the German soldiers kept them all for themselves", "the British soldiers didn't share it with the local people", "the US soldiers handed out all chocolates to people in big cities"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1402, "question": "China's former volleyball star Lang Ping has been invited to coach the US women's national team for the Beijing 2008 Olympics. But China's sports media said the offer would be difficult to accept. Lang, who is presently coaching a club team in Italy's professional volleyball league, told sina.com that she was considering the offer by the US Volleyball Association. \"Right now I'm still considering their offer but I will answer them soon,\"Lang said. \"If I don't take the job, I have to give them enough time to find someone else.\" Lang, 45,won Olympic gold in 1984. She later coached the Chinese women to silver at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics and the 1998 World Championships. She has also coached at New Mexico University in the United States where her daughter was born and lives. The reaction in t...\n\nQ: According to this passage, Lang Ping is   _   at present.", "options": ["a volleyball player", "a club coach", "an unusual player", "an assistant"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2689, "question": "Teresa was born in Yugoslavia on August 27,1910. Her parents were Albanians and member of the Roman Catholic Church. When she was seven years old, her father was murdered. She decided not to be filled with hate because of this tragedy . Instead, she would seek a life of love. This ambition led her to Ireland where she became a nun at the age of eighteen. After only one year of training, she was sent to India to teach in a school called Loretto House, where the students were mostly from rich Indian families. After 15 years there, she left her duties as a teacher to \"follow Christ into the slums .\" Her heart led her away from the rich to the needs of the poor. She was then 36 years old. Teresa no longer was affiliated with the Irish nuns who sent her to Loreto House but worked independently....\n\nQ: Why did Mother Teresa become a nun?", "options": ["Her father was killed.", "The hate of her father's death.", "She was looking for a life of love.", "The poor life of her childhood."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 570, "question": "Sheep, like turkeys and ostriches, are not considered the cleverest animals. British scientists said last Wednesday human may have underestimated the woolly creatures. They could be much smarter than we think. Researchers at the Babraham Institute in Cambridge, southern. England, have shown that animals have a good memory system and are extremely good at recognizing faces--which they think is a sure sign of intelligence. Behavioral scientist Keith Kendrick and his friends trained 20 sheep to recognize and distinguish 25 pairs of sheep faces and used electrodes to measure their brain activity, which showed they could remember 50 faces for up to two years. \"If they can do that with faces, the fact is that they have to have reasonable intelligence, otherwise, what is the point of having a sys...\n\nQ: As is shown in the passage   _  .", "options": ["sheep are among the weak animals", "it is not right for people to raise sheep in groups", "when sheep eat grass in the fields their minds may be active", "if people feel frightened, they may become more brave"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1738, "question": "Names have gained increasing importance in the competitive world of higher education. As colleges struggle for market share, they are looking for names that project the image they want or reflect the changes they hope to make. Trenton State College, for example, became the College of New Jersey nine years ago when it began raising admission standards and appealing to students from throughout the state. \"All I hear in higher education is, 'Brand, brand, brand,'\" said Tim Westerbeck, who specializes in branding and is managing director of Lippmann Hearne, a marketing firm based in Chicago that works with universities and other nonprofit organizations. \"There has been a sea change over the last 10 years. Marketing used to be almost a dirty word in higher education.\" Not all efforts at name ch...\n\nQ: It is implied that one of the most significant changes in higher education in the past decade is   _  .", "options": ["the brand", "the college name", "the concept of marketing", "list of majors"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3292, "question": "Bicycles are a great way to get around. They're fun to ride, especially down hills. And, as you speed along the road, you might also think of ways in which you could improve your bike-- make it safer, more efficient, or more comfortable. In fact, the two-wheeled machines make for some cool science projects. This year's Intel International Science and Engineering Fair (ISEF), held last May in Cleveland, featured(had)three bicycle projects from three countries. Like many of the other experiments presented at ISEF, the bike projects showed that some of the most interesting scientific research often begins by taking a closer look at things you care about. Renato Angulo Chu had even grander ambitions. The 12th-grader from Lima, Peru, wanted to _ some of his country's economic troubles. \"I see a...\n\nQ: Renato's special Multibike has all the following  EXCEPT    _  .", "options": ["making knives sharp", "mixing any kind of drinks", "producing electricity", "operating a machine with its own electricity"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 127, "question": "Three Central Texas men were honored with the Texas Department of Public Safety's Director's Award in a Tuesday morning ceremony for their heroism in saving the victims of a fiery two car accident. The accident occurred on March 25 when a vehicle lost control while traveling on a rain-soaked State Highway 6 near Baylor Camp Road. It ran into an oncoming vehicle, leaving the occupants trapped inside as both vehicles burst into flames. Bonge was the first on the scene and heard children screaming. He broke through a back window and pulled Mallory Smith, 10, and her sister, Megan Smith,9,from the wreckage. The girls' mother, Beckie Smith, was not with them at the time of the wreck, as they were traveling with their baby sitter, Lisa Bow bin. Beckie Smith still remembers the sickening feeling ...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Three persons were awarded for rescuing victims in a car accident.", "Three ordinary people were regarded as great heroes.", "Several victims were carried to safety from the burning cars.", "A car accident occurred on a rain-soaked State Highway 6."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2980, "question": "Deng Nannan, 15, used to hate drinking milk for breakfast. But she had to drink it because her mom, as well as many others, said that milk was good for her growing body. Besides, milk and bread made up a convenient diet that saved her parents a lot of time after Deng entered junior school and had to arrive at school early in the morning. After that, Mengniu and Yili became her favorite brands of morning milk and yoghurt after dinner. However, she has been forced to change her diet since the recent milk crisis. Many best-selling milk brands such as Mengniu, Yili and Bright were discovered to contain melamine , which is usually used to make plastic. The bad milk products have sickened more than 5,300 babies and killed four. \"I shifted to rice porridge,\" she said. \"My mom has to get up at 5:5...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["Deng Nannan prefers porridge to milk.", "Deng Nannan likes drinking milk all the time.", "Deng Nannan began to drink milk because of her mother's advice.", "Deng's favorite milk brands were Mengniu and Sanyuan."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 520, "question": "A recent online poll asked kids what they hated most about school. \"Classes are boring\" came in first. \"Too much homework\" was a close second. Since all activities remain interesting for only so long, too much homework can lead to ennui. So, why are some kids getting homework overload? Teachers give two reasons. First, they say, the government now requires schools to meet higher-than-ever achievement goals for students. If students don' t succeed, the school faces punishment. Second, many parents want their children to be able to get into the best colleges and universities. These parents believe homework is a way to ensure that students are learning as much as possible. People who favor homework argue that it can have many beneficial effects. They claim it can help students develop good st...\n\nQ: Those who are in favor of homework think that   _  .", "options": ["homework helps students to succeed", "it's good for kids to help each other in learning", "parents are a great help when kids do homework at home", "homework helps children to learn independently"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2252, "question": "After months of fear, hate and prosecution , the music and consumer-electronics industry decided to try to make beautiful music together. Last week the Secure Digital Music Initiative, a combination of 100 music, electronics and high-tech companies announced that it agreed on a music format known as MP3 which caused disagreement. Nowadays, more and more young people are fond of music that is played on their portable MP3 players. So this announcement attracted a lot of attention in both the producer and consumer sides. MP3 allows the digital music in CDs to be made smaller to a tenth its size and still sounds great. MP3 songs are small enough to be traded online; they are made by the millions to the _ of record companies, which fear that everything ever released on disc will end up online f...\n\nQ: The most appropriate title for the passage may be_.", "options": ["\"MP3 Clears Its Way\"", "\"Music And Electronics\"", "\"Piracy Along The Way\"", "\"Movie Is The Next\""], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1706, "question": "Dear Mr. King, Your grocery store is outstanding in many ways. I enjoy the selection of produce and fresh bakery items. I have been a long time Supermart shopper and hope to continue for many years. I have found, however, that I must make a separate shopping trip to one of your competitors because there are many items your store does not carry. This becomes inconvenient for me, as my time is valuable, and I do not like to make two trips. Your low prices and excellent customer service keep me coming back to Supermart, but I would be a more satisfied customer if I could find all the items I need in one place. Specifically, I have never been able to purchase nacho cheese soup at your store. I can find other flavors of soup, but your store does not carry nacho cheese soup, a common ingredient ...\n\nQ: From the letter, we can learn that the author is   _  .", "options": ["a very picky reporter", "a competitor of the store", "a responsible nutritionist", "a regular customer of the store"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 227, "question": "He looked like a pirate. With his handkerchief tied in a knot behind his little nine-year-old head, he looked like a pirate, a sad pirate. The first time little David came to our camp, he was hairless and worn out from medical treatments. He was also very angry. Paul Newman's camp counselors ( ) were hoping to fill David's days with fun and laughter. But David stayed inside himself, wanting to be alone, or in a corner of the cabin. At this camp for children with life-threatening illnesses, we had seen some pretty tough children worn out by cancer recover full of energy despite their illness. But we saw little progress in David no matter what we tried with him. Five days into the eight-day session saw a quiet, sad little pirate. Then something happened on that fifth night. Something at camp...\n\nQ: What can we learn from this article?", "options": ["The camp was intended for those talented in singing and dancing.", "The purpose of the camp was to give diseased children caring love.", "The camp was popular among the children who enjoyed their vacation here.", "Medical treatment could be provided to diseased children at the camp."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1205, "question": "It was 9:00 am already! Richard had to leave for work! Before leaving he hurriedly looked at the newspaper and stood still! Is he seeing it right? He rubbed his eyes and saw again... Yes, it was his name in the obituary ! He threw the paper in the bin and screamed. Richard started to recollect. He remembered that last night when he went to bed he had a chest pain and he was rushed to hospital. Then he went into a sound sleep. But what happened after that? He could suddenly see his living room filled with people... all in tears; his mom, his wife and his children. He also saw his best friend, the one he had a serious misunderstanding a few days back. He wanted to say \"Sorry\" to him... but now no one could hear his voice. He wondered how he could tell his mom that he felt so thankful to have...\n\nQ: When Richard saw his name in the newspaper, he felt   _  .", "options": ["sad", "shocked", "regretful", "worried"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2504, "question": "Dave Bruno works as an online marketing manager. Several years ago, one weekend Bruno and his family did a major house cleanup and then donated several bags of unneeded items to the local Goodwill store. \"After all were done, I looked around and realized that I still had too much stuff\", says Bruno, \" _ \" That realization prompted the 39-year-old father of three to try an experiment, \"The 100Thing Challenge\". With the goal of breaking free of what he calls a \"bad habit of consumerism , Bruno was determined to live for one year with just 100 personal items. He cut down his possessions to 94 items, including a Bible, laptop, guitar, wedding ring, car and clothes. He created some guidelines for the experiment since his wife and daughters did not participate, familyshared and household items d...\n\nQ: The things were included in Bruno's 94 items EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["socks", "a Bible", "cookers", "a wedding ring"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1882, "question": "The man from the west stopped and drew back his arm. \"You're not Jimmy Wells,\" he said in a quick and angry way, \"Twenty years is a long time, but not long enough to change a man' nose from a Roman to pug.\" \"It sometimes changes a good man into a bad one,\" said the tall man, \"you've been under arrest for ten minutes. Silky Bob. prefix = st1 /Chicagothinks you may have dropped over our way and phones us she wants to have a word with you. Going quietly, are you? That's sensible. Now before we go to the station here's a note I was asked to hand you. You may read it here at the window. It's from Patrolman Wells.?\" The man from the West opened the little piece of paper handed him. His hand was steady when he began to read, but it trembled a little by the time he finished. The note was rather sh...\n\nQ: The man from the West recognized the tall man not to be the one he had been waiting for because the tall man   _  .", "options": ["had a different accent from his", "had a different nose from his friend's", "was his another old friend", "said \"Chicagowants to talk with you?\""], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3183, "question": "Instagram is a fast,beautiful and fun way to share your life with friends and family.Take a picture or video,choose a filter to transform its look and feel.and then post to Instagram--it's that easy.You can even share to Facebook.Twitter and more.It's a new way to see the world.So many photos of food are contained on Instagram--now a pop-up diner in London is taking advantage of this new trend by letting people settle the bill for their meals simply by uploading photos of their dishes to social networks. I always thought people's taking pictures of their food was kind of silly, but at this new pop-up restaurant in the UK,I'd probably do it too.\"The Picture House\"is the world's first pay-by-photo restaurant--you order, click a photo of the food,share on Instagram and eat for free! The resta...\n\nQ: \"The Picture House\"encourages sharing photos of its food to  _  .", "options": ["raise the price of frozen food", "attract more customers", "create a new social media trend", "reward the regular customers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 668, "question": "Since people first sent rockets into space in the 1950s, we have been leaving behind all sorts of things. Some of them, like the camera, were lost by astronauts while they did work outside their spaceship. But much of the space junk is made up of little pieces of things that were once bigger objects, until they struck each other and broke apart. Some things we send into space fall back toward the earth and burn up in the atmosphere. But larger pieces sometimes survive the extreme heat and hit the ground or the ocean at great speeds. So there is always concern that something may fall from the sky and do some harm. But space junk falling on housetops is not the biggest worry. Scientists are concerned about what happens when an empty rocket strikes another while orbiting the earth. Two big th...\n\nQ: Much of the space junk   _  .", "options": ["was thrown by the astronauts", "is from broken spaceship", "is made up of small pieces of things", "returns to the earth piece by piece"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2511, "question": "A pair of pandas being lent by China to Japan was set to arrive in Tokyo's Ueno Zoo in the Japanese capital and raising hopes that the animals may help improve bilateral ties. Bi Li and his female partner, Xian Nu, both 5, were due to at Narita international Airport in Tokyo on a flight from Shanghai. Together with their keeper, the pair were transferred from Chengdu, to Shanghai on Monday morning, said Li Desheng, deputy chief of the Wolong Nature Reserve. The pair, which are young adults, will be the first pandas at Ueno Zoo since April 2008, when the institution's beloved Ling Ling died. Ueno Zoo had spent 90 million yen ($1.1 million) installing under-floor heating, a playground with a sandbox and landscaping. The pair will dine on rare bamboo from the central Japanese mountain of Izu ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we know that Ling Ling stayed in Japan for about    _    .", "options": ["5 years", "10 years", "15 years", "20 years"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 684, "question": "For the first time in Hong Kong's history, an entertainer has been written into middle school textbooks. He is considered one of the best actors in Hong Kong. Yes, he is Chow Yun-fat. The example of his long hard struggle for success has been used in a chapter in a Hong Kong middle school textbook. Using his experience, students can learn to make the most of their time and to grab every opportunity to succeed. On hearing about this, Chow said happily, \"I really hope that my experiences can make young people understand that one should not be afraid of difficulties and setbacks , for they are the only way to success.\" Indeed, Chow has travelled a long and difficult path to reach his success. In 1955, he was born into a poor family in Hong Kong. When he was 17, he had to leave school. He work...\n\nQ: The author wrote this passage to   _  .", "options": ["introduce Chow's films", "praise Chow for his excellent performance", "call on people to learn from Chow", "show why Chow is popular"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2817, "question": "The idea of light pollution has developed with the increase of lights in cities. In many areas, this light makes it difficult or impossible to observe stars and planets in the night sky. There are a number of reasons why light pollution is important. One has become clear at the Mount Wilson Observatory near Los Angeles, California. Today, light from Los Angeles makes the night sky above Mount Wilson very bright. It is no longer an important reasearch center because of light pollution. Light pollution threatens to reduce the scientific value of research telescoples in other important observatories. They include Lick Observatory near San Jose, California and Yerkes Observatory near Chicago, Illionis. Light pollution is the result of wasted energy. Bright light that shines into the sky is not...\n\nQ: The victims affected by the light pollution are  _  .", "options": ["children", "grownups", "students", "observatories"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 39, "question": "The first time Luca heard the Island of Inventions, he was very young, but the wonders he heard about sounded so unbelievable to him that they were forever kept in his memory. Since then, he never stopped searching clues which might lead him to that place of wonder. He read widely to collect information. Taking a little from here and there, he got quite a clear idea of what the Island was really like. It was a secret place, where all the great men learn and invent together. To be able to join that select club, you had to have created great inventions. Only then could you receive the invitation. To get a chance, Luca spend the years studying and inventing. Every new idea he got, he made it into an invention, and if there were anything he didn't understand, he would seek help. Soon he met ot...\n\nQ: Luca read widely to   _  .", "options": ["get information about the great inventions", "get clear ideas about the island for vacations", "seek massages about the secret club of inventions", "get more knowledge for the benefit of his inventions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3003, "question": "Events Calendar TUESDAY Landscape Pests Learn to identify, control and prevent seasonal landscape-disease and landscape-pest problems at the workshop, 3:30 pm. - 5 pm. Tuesday at the US National Arboretum, 3501 New York Ave NE, Washington. $15; registration required. 202-245-4521 or www.usna.usda.gov. THROUGH AUGUST 3 Horticultural Art Watercolors, pen-and-ink drawings and colored-pencil pieces by the Brookside Gardens School of Botanical Art and Illustration will be on display at the exhibit Botanic 2007: The Art and Science of Plants at Brookside Gardens Visitors Center, 1800 Glenallan Ave, Wheaton, through Aug. 3. Free. 301-962-1400 or www.brooksidegardens.org. THROUGH SEPTEMBER 9 Botanical Art Visit Patterns in Nature, an exhibit by Amy Lamb featuring photographs of flowers, leaves and...\n\nQ: From the advertisement, we learn   _  .", "options": ["the first event is about growing healthy plants", "all of the events are free of charge", "there is no time limit to all the events", "you can find the information of all the events either by phone or by e-mail"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3497, "question": "Do you know how to play a game called \"Musical Chairs\"?It is easy to play and most people enjoy it. All you need are some chairs, some people and some way of making music. You may use a piano or any other musical instrument, if someone can play it. You may use a tape recorder. You can even use a radio. Put the chairs in a row. The chairs may be put in twos, back to back. A better way is to have the chairs in one row with each chair facing in the opposite direction to the chair next to it. The game is easy. When the music starts, the players walk round the chairs. Everyone goes in the same direction, of course, they should walk in time to the music. If the music is fast they should walk quickly. If the music is slow, they should walk slowly. The person playing music cannot see the people in...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The game \"Musical Chairs\" is not difficult to learn.", "The last one can sit on the last chair.", "The winner can sit on the chair.", "If the person plays music, he cannot be the winner."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2336, "question": "How do you get a man to do his share of the house work? If you are like most of the women, you will face the question the hard way. A man will enjoy a clean, orderly house, but he usually won't make the effort to clean or organize it. This doesn't mean that a woman has to do all the housework; she may have to manage many of household duties, and request his partner's participation. A woman can often say that men and women should take equal responsibility for housework. Very few men are raised to be fully responsible for housework, and many men look on housework as women's work. On the other hand, most men will readily work around the yard, make repairs and complete projects on weekends or evenings, and it's important that you give your man appreciation for those things too. Most man will t...\n\nQ: In order to get men to do some housework, women should often   _", "options": ["order them to do their share.", "ask them to do some housework politely", "blame men's laziness", "monitor men's work"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3044, "question": "If you want to pay a visit to Iceland, you'll enter a whole new region of experience. You'll discover original nature as you've never seen it before. The freedom to wander in the city or the wilds as you please is the key to the Iceland experience. Reykjavik, the capital of Iceland, is just a part of the Icelandic experience with its midnight sun or the magical landscapes mixed with ice and fire. Reykjavik has a population of around 170,000 and offers an interesting mix of culture and local village roots. Old accounts say the ancient gods themselves guided Iceland's first settler to make his home in Reykjavik. He named the place Reykjavik (Steamy Bay)after the geothermal steam he saw, which today heats homes and outdoor swimming pools throughout the city, a pollution-free energy source tha...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that_.", "options": ["people living in Reykiavik seldom get heat from coal.", "hotel accommodation is so rare that visitors usually camp in the city's biggest parks.", "all visitors must dine out while visiting Iceland.", "you have to walk a short distance if you want to go sightseeing outside the city."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1144, "question": "A Scottish woman has given birth to twins for the third time. Karen Rodger, 41, welcomed her first pair of girls rowan and Isla after having twice given birth to twin boys. \"I still haven't really taken it on board because I was convinced I was having two boys,\" Rodger told Sky News. Karen said her husband Colin was equally stunned when the couple learned they were going to have their fifth and sixth child. \"He thought I was joking and immediately wrote back to say 'this is not funny'. I had to explain that it really was true,\" Karen said. The average couple has about a 3 percent chance of having twins when not accounting for fertility drugs. And with each following pregnancy, the changes of producing twins a second, or even third time, become less. Karen, a dance lecturer, first learned o...\n\nQ: After reading the passage, we know that Karen   _  .", "options": ["gave birth to the twin girls in her forties", "now has three boys and three girls in total", "was talked into having more kids by her husband", "hoped she could have more girls soon"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2032, "question": "Is your family interested in buying a dog? A dog can be a pleasant companion to your family, but if you choose the wrong kind of dog , you will have a lot of troubles. Families should sit down and discuss the possible problems before buying a dog. Even if the children in your family are the ones who want the dog, the parents are the ones who are really responsible for seeing that the animal is properly cared for. If you don't know much about dogs, it is a good idea to go to the library for books about different kinds of dogs, and books about how to train a young dog. In reading about the different breeds you should know that a dog described as very alert may be too active. When a book describes a dog as an excellent hunting dog, it probably means that the dog won't be happy living in a sma...\n\nQ: Which is the best topic of the passage?", "options": ["The care and proper selection of dogs for families.", "Different breeds of dogs.", "Responsibility for seeing that dogs are properly cared for.", "Different kinds of books about dogs."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2041, "question": "I arrived at the bus station much too early for the London bus, which was not to leave until five to twelve. I pushed through the crowds, looking for somewhere to sit down. Scores of people were standing about, or struggling along with their bags and the cases to find the right lines. There was a party of school girls. I could see teachers trying to keep them in order. But there was nowhere for me to sit. I stepped into the station buffet. I looked up at the clock there. It was only twenty to twelve. I found a seat opposite a large mirror on the wall. Just then a friend of mine called Jim came in and sat with me. \"What time is your bus?\" asked Jim. \"Oh, there's a plenty of time yet,\" I answered. \"Oh, I'll get some drinks then,\" said Jim. We talked while drinking. Then I looked at the clock...\n\nQ: The writer went to the station buffet because   _  .", "options": ["he was thirsty", "he saw the station buffet was not so crowded", "it was still early for his bus and he couldn't find a place to sit at the bus station", "he had changed his mind; he wouldn't go to London"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3037, "question": "Once upon a time a peacock and a tortoise became great friends. The peacock lived in a tree on the bank of the stream in which the tortoise had his home, and every day the peacock danced near the stream and displayed his gay plumage for the amusement of his friend. Unfortunately, one day a bird-catcher caught the peacock and was about to take him away to the market. The unhappy bird begged his captor to allow him to say goodbyeto his friend -- the tortoise. The bird-catcher agreed and took the peacock to the tortoise, who was greatly astonished when he saw his friend become a captive. The tortoise asked the bird-catcher to let the peacock go, but the bird-catcher laughed at his request, saying that was his livelihood. The tortoise then said, \"If I give you a handsome present, will you let ...\n\nQ: Why did the bird-catcher come back to the tortoise?", "options": ["Because he wanted to win a match.", "Because he thought the pearl didn't suit him.", "Because he wanted to thank the tortoise.", "Because he wanted to get one more pearl."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 446, "question": "The challenge to drink to the limits of one's endurance has become a celebrated part of college life. In one of the most extensive reports on college drinking thus far, a 1997 Harvard School of Public Health study found that 43 percent of college students admitted binge drinking in the preceding two weeks (Defined as four drinks in a sitting for a woman and five of a man, a drinking binge is when one drinks enough to risk health and well - being ) Experts estimate that excessive drinking is involved in thousands of student deaths a year. And the Harvard researchers found that there has been a dramatic change in why students drink. 39 percent drank \"to get drunk\" in 1993, but 52 percent had the same objective in 1997. \"What has changed is the across - the - board acceptability of intoxicati...\n\nQ: Students regard drinking and binge drinking as_.", "options": ["tolerable", "acceptable", "necessary", "essential"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2082, "question": "Monkeys are very similar to us in many ways. We enjoy watching them because they often act like us. In fact, scientists say monkeys and humans share a common ancestor. Monkeys make us smile, too, because they are creatures full of playful tricks. This is why many monkey expressions are about tricky people or playful acts. One of these expressions is monkeyshines, meaning tricks or foolish acts. So, when a teacher says to a group of students: \"Stop those monkeyshines right now!\", you know that the kids are playing, instead of studying. You might hear that same teacher warn a student not to monkey around with a valuable piece of equipment. You monkey around with something when you are touching or playing with something you should leave alone. Also, you can monkey around when you feel like do...\n\nQ: The expression \"monkeyshine\" has the closest meaning to   _  .", "options": ["mischief", "laziness", "making noise", "diligence"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 812, "question": "Have you heard of the scandal that happened in one of Great Britain's biggest supermarket chains called Tesco? The British love Tesco as it sells very cheap products and it can be found on almost every corner of a British city or town. On January 15th 2013 food inspectors discovered 30 % horsemeat in a certain brand of frozen beefburgers that were mostly sold by Tesco in the UK and Ireland. In times of social media like Facebook and Twitter the news has spread fast and customers have been very concerned about what the food they buy actually contains. Tesco said it had taken away the burgers from the shop shelves immediately, and apologized to their customers. They also promised that they would find out what exactly happened and that they would work harder than ever so this would never happ...\n\nQ: What is the scandal?", "options": ["Tesco's products were much more expensive than they are supposed to be.", "Tesco didn't react immediately to a food quality issue.", "Tesco sold expired food.", "Horsemeat was found in burgers sold in Tesco."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2111, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting. He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life. He is _ for news all the time, then after several years he may get a desk job, and life becomes a bit more settled. Let's look at his work a little more closely. In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match. Sometimes he may be so busy that he has hardly any time to sleep. And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty-handed. In the beginning, a reporter has to cover a very wide field. After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work. For example, he may finally be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports. Some reporters may...\n\nQ: From the passage we can infer that, to be a good reporter, he must be all of the following except   _  .", "options": ["brave", "quick in mind", "strong", "well-informed"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 68, "question": "School is out for the summer in some areas, and for many children, that means weeks of sleeping in late, trips to the swimming pool or hours spent in front of the TV. These months of inactivity--- away from the daily tiring things of school--- are something that young people look forward to, but it can have a detrimental influence on the knowledge they have. Studies have shown that children lose a lot in math skills during the summer months. Children who spend little time learning experience a much greater amount of learning loss than those who often take part in summer programs. So when school starts again in the fall, teachers often have to spend several weeks reteaching children material that they have forgotten. Experts suggest that parents make sure the summer months are a time of con...\n\nQ: Children lose a lot in learning in the summer break because they_.", "options": ["do homework before the TV", "stay up late at night", "visit the swimming pool", "spend little time learning"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3099, "question": "An English saying goes: \" _ \" That means we should relax after a day's hard work or we'll be unhealthy. Many students know that if they want to get ideal jobs with good salaries, they must do well in high school so they can enter good universities. Therefore, they spend all day studying without time to relax. However, not all students can go to top universities even if they work very hard. Students are pressurized by parents and teachers who are just concerned about their studies and exam scores while ignoring their hobbies and individual differences. As a result, students are forces to work harder and harder. Furthermore, there is pressure coming from students themselves. They realize they have a slim chance of getting into a top university as competition is fierce. So, they put a lot of ...\n\nQ: What causes the student' pressure from themselves?", "options": ["That they don't know how to get top universities.", "That they want to relax but have no chance.", "That they fail to relax themselves during their work.", "That they think too much about the result of their work."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 496, "question": "Warm weather brought by El Nino has had mixed effects on animals in usually snowy places in North America, including New England, according to an Associated Press article. Some animals seem to benefit from having a chance to gather more food before winter, and from expending less energy in daily survival mode. Others, like snowshoe hares, are put at center stage in predators' view when they lack snow for disguising their white fur -- not a good thing for them, of course. Black bears, on the other hand, have been keeping busy gathering nuts and apples, when they would normally have settled into their winter homes by now. Vermont and Massachusetts officials have asked residents to wait till snow falls to take out their bird feeders for the sake of safety, the article said. \"We suggest waitin...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the proper title for the passage?", "options": ["Warm Weather Helps Animals Survive", "Snow Amounts Determine Animals' Winter Life", "Measures Should Be Taken to Protect Wildlife", "Lack of Snow Affects North American Animals"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1793, "question": "Have you ever wanted to achieve a goal and ended up doing tons of research on how to achieve the goal? As you learn more and more, it feels like you know less and less because when you learn something new, you find that there is a lot to know about those things. Sometimes, people will get stuck in this needing to gather more and more information. There's nothing wrong with learning a lot, but when you let learning get in the way of doing, you will never get going. When you never get going, you still never start having the things you want. Too much learning can paralyze you in terms of taking action. A better way to go about achieving a goal is to gather some information and immediately start taking action on the information you have gathered. Many times you will feel unprepared, and that's...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we'd better learn from  _  .", "options": ["our experiences", "adequate preparations", "other people who have succeeded", "the information we have gathered"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1863, "question": "Polynesian Cultural Center The Polynesian Cultural Center (P.C.C.) offers the best value for your vacation dollar. There is so much to see and do for the entire family. They offer a unique and authentic view not only of the Hawaiian culture, but also offer a taste of their Polynesian cuisines . The Gateway Buffet Package A fun activity for all ages, experience the beauty of true Polynesia with The Polynesian Cultural Center's newest package. Experience the 7 Polynesian Islands as they share with you their culture through song and dance. Enjoy Prime Rib & Seafood Dinner at the Gateway Restaurant, finishing the evening with the Horizons Night Show. Adult Price: $68.00 Child Price: $51.00 The Twilight Package--Ambassador's Fine Dining This activity is an excellent choice for those who want a ...\n\nQ: How many kinds of cuisines are mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["One.", "Two.", "Three.", "Four."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1204, "question": "In a world with limited land, water and other natural resources, the harm from the traditional business model is on the rise. Actually, the past decade has seen more and more forests disappearing and the globe becoming increasingly warm. People now realize that this unhealthy situation must be changed, and that we must be able to develop in sustainable ways. That means growth with low carbon or development of sustainable products. In other words, we should keep the earth healthy while using its supply of natural resources. Today, sustainable development is a proper trend in many countries. According to a recent study, the global market for low-carbon energy will become three times bigger over the next decade. China, for example, has set its mind on leading that market, hoping to seize chan...\n\nQ: What is the main purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To advocate sustainable development.", "To compare two business models.", "To predict a change of the global market.", "To introduce a new business model."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1506, "question": "Since my son is getting ready for first grade, I asked a friend where she shops for school supplies. For price and convenience, she had a quick answer: schoolpak.com. Parents can buy items or packaged equipment for all grades. The Generic Elementary School-pak for first through fifth graders, for example, is $23.28. (Teachers can also e-mail their grade's or school's whole list for a price on customized kits . Shipping is free for 75 or more kits) _ Teachers thinks highly of educationalwarehouse.com for its learning tools and games--everything from puzzles and puppets to software and chalks.Classroomdirect.com has great prices on over 10.000 products and a special corner offering even deeper discounts. Pick your lunch box The second-most-difficult back-to-school decision, right after what ...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly aimed at  _  .", "options": ["parents", "teachers", "students", "businessmen"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1482, "question": "A survey reveals that employees in China say they are not engaged in their jobs. Judging by the survey data, many Chinese workplaces are black holes of misery and despair. Only 6% of Chinese employees said they are \"engaged\" in their jobs, according to a global Gallup survey released this month. China's numbers equal the numbers out of war-weary Iraq. Workers across all income levels and industries were surveyed by Gallup in China, defined by Gallup to mean they were \"psychologically committed to their jobs and likely to be making positive contributions to their organizations\". Out of 94 countries polled, only six countries scored lower rates of job engagement than China, including Tunisia, Israel and Syria. Unsurprisingly, 0% of Syrians admitted to being engaged at work. In a related surv...\n\nQ: According to the author, why most Chinese dislike their jobs?", "options": ["Because they don't take the jobs they really like", "Because many Chinese workplaces are full of misery and despair.", "Because they have no choice but to choose the stable jobs.", "Because they are not psychologically committed to their jobs."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2643, "question": "What teaches you more about China: learning the language or making friends with Chinese people? Doing both would be perfect of course and maybe some people would say you cannot separate the two. I arrived in China in September 2010 and have been fortunate over the last year to teach English at a small university in Zhejiang province,about half an hour from Hangzhou.Despite starting with the best of aims to learn Chinese.in each term something seemed to prevent me.In the first term it was a bad cold and judging some public English speech contests,and then my father's death sent me home for a while. But if I miss Chinese lessons this year I will make friends with several of the Chinese teachers at the university who also teach English.It's been a wonderful thing to be welcomed into their liv...\n\nQ: Which country may the author come from?", "options": ["Russia.", "America.", "Japan", "Korea."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2750, "question": "Science Daily (Apr. 27, 2008)-- Dutch ecologist Roxina Soler and her colleagues have discovered that subterranean and aboveground herbivorous insects can communicate with each other by using plants as telephones. Subterranean insects issue chemical warning signals through the leaves of the plant. This way, aboveground insects are warned that the plant is already \"occupied\". Aboveground, leaf-eating insects prefer plants that have not yet been occupied by subterranean root-eating insects. Subterranean insects send out chemical signals through the leaves of the plant, which warn the aboveground insects about their presence. This messaging makes it possible for spatially-separated insects to avoid each other, so that they do not compete for, the same plant. In recent years it has been discove...\n\nQ: After finding a plant occupied by root-eating insects, aboveground insects will usually   _  .", "options": ["send out warning signals", "choose to leave the plant", "compete for the same plant", "fight with the root-eating insects"], "answer": 1}]